Contact

parashar.ashu168@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ashutoshparashar-1608 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Fundamental Analysis
DCF Valuation
Portfolio Management

Certifications

Excel Crash Course
Microsoft Excel: Advanced
Financial Accounting Fundamentals
Essentials Of Corporate Finance
Specialisation
Technical Analysis

Honors-Awards
2nd Position

Ashutosh Parashar

Valuation and Modeling | Macroeconomics | Interned@ IIFL and Finlatics | Aspiring Investment Analyst/Manager Patna

Summary

"If It Is To Be It's Up To Me."

Coming from not a very privileged background, I don't have a great college to show off but everyday, I try to more than make up for it by putting in 100% of my efforts in learning and growing.

I can proudly say that most of what I have learned has come from YouTube/Coursera/Udemy and it has opened my mind to an extent which I never thought would happen.

Currently in the final year of my undergraduate degree in economics, I have over time grown very curious about finance and where it crosses path with economics. Investment management, investment research and investment banking are some of the areas I am interested in and I am working continuously on improving my skills that are needed to achieve goals not only in professional life but personal life also.

I have also developed a free website(econalpha.ga) from scratch (guess what? using various tutorials on YouTube) to take online whatever I have learned about economics in the past few years. It feeds into my love for writing on economy and markets as well. The website isn't rich in content as of now but I am working on it.

If you have made this far then I thank you for your time and attention.

Experience

Finlatics

Equity Research and Portfolio Management Intern June 2020 - August 2020 (3 months)

IIFL (India Infoline Group)
Financial Management Intern
April 2020 - June 2020 (3 months)

Learning and researching on investment avenues in capital markets.

Citi

Institutional Banking Virtual Intern April 2020 - May 2020 (2 months)

Completed a virtual internship program at Citi which included training in company and industry analysis, comps analysis, DCF modelling and market outperformance.

EconAlpha

Founder

February 2020 - May 2020 (4 months)

Future Impact Investment Management Virtual Intern April 2020 - April 2020 (1 month)

Education

Magadh University

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Economics · (2017 - 2020)

Central Board of Secondary Education

XII · (2015 - 2017)

Central Board of Secondary Education

X · (2015 - 2015)